yupptv.com 2008-12-17

# YuppTV Privacy Policy

| 

1\. PRIVACY POLICY

By using the Global Takeoff our website, the User consents to the collection, use, and storage of User information by Global Takeoff in the manner described in this Privacy Policy and elsewhere on the Global Takeoff sites. This Privacy Policy applies only to information Global Takeoff and the Services collects about the User and does not apply to information about the User collected by Global Takeoffs affiliated providers or third party websites and offerings linked to or otherwise accessible from the Global Takeoff website or the Services. The information collected or received by Global Takeoffs affiliated providers and/ or third parties are subject to their own privacy policies.

This Privacy Policy details important information regarding the use and disclosure of User information collected on the Global Takeoff sites to enable the User to make an informed decision about whether to use or continue using the Global Takeoff sites and the Services.

It is clarified that any video, image, or other User Content posted at the direction of the User onto the Global Takeoff site and the Services becomes published content and shall not be considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Policy.

2\. COLLECTION OF INFORMATION

The information gathered by Global Takeoff may either be information that the User voluntarily supplies to Global Takeoff when the User registers or initiates transactions with the Services and/ or information gathered on usage patterns and preferences as the User navigates through Global Takeoffs sites and/ or uses the Services. An agent or affiliate of Global Takeoff may, at times and on being so authorized, collect information on behalf of Global Takeoff. Third party providers featured on or linked to by the Global Takeoff sites, such as vendors of products and services offered through the sites, may be gathering the same kinds of information. 

User provided Information. To make use of certain features on the Global Takeoff sites and to use the Services and when choosing to participate in various activities on the Global Takeoff sites such as uploading videos, posting messages, entering contests or sweepstakes, taking advantage of promotions, responding to surveys, or subscribing to newsletters or other mailing lists, the User may be required to register and/ or provide certain personally identifiable information as part of the participation/ registration process. Global Takeoff may also ask for information from Users who buy products or services or conduct other transactions on its sites. 

Any personal information or video content that the User voluntarily discloses online (on discussion boards, in messages and chat areas, etc.) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others. The Users account name (not the email address) is displayed to other Users when any videos are uploaded or messages are sent through the Services and other Users can contact the User through messages and comments. Any videos that the User submits to the Global Takeoff sites may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public. 

Cookies. To enable Global Takeoff to make its sites more responsive to the needs of the Users, Global Takeoff may use a standard feature of browser software called a "cookie," to assign each visitor a unique, random number, a type of user ID that may reside on the Users computer. The cookie doesn't actually identify the User but identifies only the computer that is used to access the site. Advertisers and other third parties that provide products or services through the Global Takeoff site may also assign their own cookies to the Users browser and such process is beyond Global Takeoffs control. Global Takeoff may use both session cookies (which are temporary and disappear after the User closes the browser) and persistent cookies (which remain after the User closes the browser and which may be used by the Users browser on subsequent visits to the site). The User may reset the web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the Global Takeoff sites may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled.

Other Methods. The Global Takeoff web pages may contain electronic images (called "single-pixel GIFs" or "web beacons") that allow Global Takeoff and its affiliates to count users who have visited particular pages or to access certain cookies. These tools and other technologies to may be used to recognize which pages users visit, and which links they click on. These features may also be included in email newsletters so that Global Takeoff may learn which messages have been opened and acted upon. These tools may also enable Global Takeoff to verify online purchases by the User from the Global Takeoff sites or from third party sites that have agreed to share such information with Global Takeoff.

Browser Level Information and IP Addresses. The Global Takeoff web servers automatically collect limited information about the Users computer configuration, including browser software, the operating system, the website that referred the User, and the Users Internet Protocol (IP) address browser language, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, the order of those pages, and the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time of the Users request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify the Users browser.  
Third Party. Global Takeoff may permit third-party ad servers or ad networks, to display advertisements within the Global Takeoff sites. Such third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to the Users your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the Global Takeoff sites and automatically receive the Users IP address when this happens. The third party may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content the User sees. The User should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt-out of certain practices. Global Takeoffs privacy policy does not apply to, and Global Takeoff cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

3\. STORAGE OF INFORMATION

Any information provided by the User to Global Takeoff shall be stored and held under generally accepted standards of technology and operational security in order to protect the Users personally identifiable information from loss, misuse, alteration, or destruction. Only authorized personnel are permitted access to the User information and these personnel are required to treat this information as confidential. Despite these precautions, Global Takeoff cannot guarantee that any and all unauthorized access to the Users information will be prevented. 

All classifieds, User Content, postings, etc. are stored in the Global Takeoff database, even after "deletion," and may be archived elsewhere and the web logs and other records are stored indefinitely. Search engines and other sites not affiliated with Global Takeoff - including archive.org, google.com, etc. may archive or otherwise make available Global Takeoff postings.

4\. USAGE OF INFORMATION

Global Takeoff uses IP address information for systems administration and trouble shooting purposes. This information is also used to deliver web pages to the User upon request; to tailor the site to the interests of the users and to measure traffic within the Global Takeoff site.

Any personally identifiable information provided by the User is used to operate, maintain, and provide the User with the features and functionality of the Global Takeoff sites.   
Global Takeoff does not use the Users email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without the Users consent except as part of a program or feature for which the User may exercise an option to not receive such messages. Global Takeoff may, however, use the Users email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes. 

Global Takeoff may use both personally identifiable information and certain non-personally-identifiable information to improve the quality and design of the Services and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing User preferences and trends.  
Global Takeoff uses cookies, clear gifs, and log file information to: remember information so that the User is not required to re-enter it during subsequent visits; provide custom and personalized content and information; monitor the effectiveness of marketing campaigns; monitor logs such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.; and to track entries, submissions, and status in promotions, sweepstakes, and contests of the User. 

5\. DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION

Affiliates. Global Takeoff may share certain types of information such as account information, diagnostic information, transaction information, and usage information with subsidiaries, affiliated companies, or other businesses or persons for the purpose of processing such information on its behalf. Global Takeoff requires such affiliates to process such information in compliance with this Privacy Policy and shall undertake all reasonable efforts to limit their use of such information and to use other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

Third Parties. Global Takeoff does not share the Users personally identifiable information with third-party companies or organizations for their commercial or marketing use without the Users express consent except as part of a specific program or feature for which the User has the ability to opt-in or opt-out. Global Takeoff may share non-personally-identifiable information with interested third-parties to assist them in understanding the usage patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality on the Global Takeoff sites and the Services. Global Takeoff may use the information to present offers to the User on behalf of business partners and advertisers. These business partners and advertisers may receive aggregate data about groups of Global Takeoff but do not receive information that personally identifies the User  
Transactions/Requests with Third Parties. The User may choose to use the Services to purchase goods/services from third party providers. Global Takeoff may share necessary information with third parties to fulfill a transaction the User has requested. Global Takeoff may share information where the User has consented to the sharing of such information, or except as described in this Privacy Policy.

Legal Obligations/Fraud. Global Takeoff may be required to may disclose such records as it believes in good faith to be appropriate or necessary to protect its legitimate business interests, safeguard others, or respond to legal process like subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process, or to establish or exercise its legal rights or defend against legal claims. The information may also be required to be disclosed in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of TOU, or as otherwise required or permitted by law.

Statistical Information. Much of the information Global Takeoff collects is in the form of aggregated statistics, such as the traffic that visits various pages within the Services, the habits and preferences of the audience, etc. Such aggregated information does not include any personally identifiable information and Global Takeoff may use such aggregated information and/ or disclose it to third parties as it deems fit. 

6\. FINANCIAL INFORMATION

Global Takeoff does not store credit card information and other financial data. Credit card transactions are transmitted to a financial gateway, and Global Takeoff endeavors to protect the security of the Users payment information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology. Global Takeoff will not disclose to third parties the Users your credit card information or other financial data except to the extent necessary to complete the transaction initiated by the User.

For e-commerce transactions, Global Takeoff may transmit the Users billing information using encryption which scrambles the credit card number and personal information. However, since no security system is impenetrable, Global Takeoff cannot guarantee the security of its databases, nor can it guarantee that information supplied by the User won't be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet.  

7\. SECURITY OF INFORMATION

Global Takeoff has established safeguards to help prevent unauthorized access to or misuse of User information, but cannot guarantee that such information will never be disclosed in a manner inconsistent with this Privacy Policy. To protect the Users privacy and security, Global Takeoff may use passwords to help verify the Users identity before granting access or making corrections to any User information.  
Global Takeoff uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of User information. Global Takeoff, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information transmitted to Global Takeoff by the User and is transmitted at the Users own risk. Once Global Takeoff receives the transmission of information, Global Takeoff makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of its systems. However, Global Takeoff cannot a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.

If Global Takeoff becomes aware of a security systems breach, then Global Takeoff may attempt to notify the User electronically so that the User can take appropriate protective steps or may post a notice on the Global Takeoff sites. Depending on where the User resides, the User may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive a free written notice of a security breach (or to withdraw consent from receiving electronic notice) the User should notify Global Takeoff using the contact form.

8\. USER CHOICES 

The User may decline to submit personally identifiable information through the Global Takeoff sites, in which case Global Takeoff may not be able to provide certain services. If the User opts to register with and provide information to Global Takeoff, the User will have the opportunity to unsubscribe, review, update, or delete the information provided at any time. If the User opts to remove registration information completely, the User may not be able to continue using certain services that require registration.   
To protect the Users privacy and security, Global Takeoff takes reasonable steps (such as requesting a unique password) to verify the Users identity before granting profile access or making corrections. The User is responsible for maintaining the secrecy of the unique password and account information at all times.

It is clarified that media files uploaded by Users to the Global Takeoff sites and the Services cannot be removed and remain subject to the TOU.  
The User may contact Global Takeoff with any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, personal information, User consent, or opt-in or opt-out choices using the contact form.

9\. CHILDRENS PRIVACY

Global Takeoffs websites are not intentionally designed for or directed at persons less than 18 years of age. Global Takeoff does not knowingly permit any person who is under 18 years of age to register with the Services or to provide any other personally identifying information. Any person under 18 years of age visiting the Global Takeoff sites is prohibited from accessing or using the Services in any manner and at any time. If Global Takeoff becomes aware that any personally identifiable information of persons less than 18 years of age has been collected on the Global Takeoffs sites without verified parental consent, then Global Takeoff will take the appropriate steps to delete any such information.

10\. INTERNATIONAL USERS  

The Global Takeoff websites may be viewed and hosted anywhere in the world, including countries that may not have specific laws regulating the collection, use and transfer of personally identifiable data. By using the Global Takeoff sites and the Services and submitting such information on it, the User voluntarily consents to such transborder transfers and hosting of such information. By visiting the Global Takeoff websites and providing information, the User acknowledges and agrees that due to the international dimension of Global Takeoff, it may use the information collected for the purposes identified in this policy or in our other communications with the User, including the transmission of information to outside the Users resident jurisdiction. A User accessing the Global Takeoff sites from any location outside the United States with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use and disclosure that differ from United States laws, such user is advised that through continued use of the Global Takeoff sites, which are governed by U.S. law, this Privacy Policy and the TOU, the User is consenting to the transfer of personal information to the United States.  

11\. CHANGE IN CONTROL 

In the event that Global Takeoff is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, Global Takeoff reserves the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information collected from the Users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the event of bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, Global Takeoff may not be able to control how the your personal information is treated, transferred, or used.

12\. MODIFICATIONS

Global Takeoff may update or revise this Privacy Policy from time to time and the User is advised to review this Policy periodically. Any significant changes to Global Takeoffs information practices will be intimated to the User with appropriate online notice. The Users continued use of the Global Takeoff sites constitutes the Users agreement to this Privacy Policy and any future modifications/revisions.

13\. CONTACT INFORMATION

Users may contact Global Takeoff with any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy using the contact form or may address such queries and / or comments to info@globaltakeoff.com

|
